{
    "Questions":[
        {
            "question": "what is your name",
            "choice": ["Gam","Yam","don't know","It's your"],
            "answer": "It's your"
        },
        {
            "question": "2+2",
            "choice": ["1","2","3","4"],
            "answer": "4"
        },
        {
            "question": "1+1",
            "choice": ["1","2","3","4"],
            "answer": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "3+3",
            "choice": ["1","2","3","6"],
            "answer": "6"
        },
        {
            "question": "4+4",
            "choice": ["1","2","8","4"],
            "answer": "8"
        },
        {
            "question": "5+5",
            "choice": ["1","10","3","4"],
            "answer": "4"
        },
        {
            "question": "6+6",
            "choice": ["1","12","3","4"],
            "answer": "12"
        },
        {
            "question": "7+7",
            "choice": ["14","2","3","4"],
            "answer": "14"
        },
        {
            "question": "8+8",
            "choice": ["16","2","3","4"],
            "answer": "16"
        },
        {
            "question": "9+9",
            "choice": ["18","2","3","4"],
            "answer": "18"
        },
        {
            "question": "10+10",
            "choice": ["1","20","3","4"],
            "answer": "20"
        },
        {
            "question": "11+11",
            "choice": ["1","22","3","4"],
            "answer": "22"
        },
        {
            "question": "12+12",
            "choice": ["1","2","3","24"],
            "answer": "24"
        },
        {
            "question": "13+13",
            "choice": ["1","26","3","4"],
            "answer": "26"
        },
        {
            "question": "14+14",
            "choice": ["1","28","3","4"],
            "answer": "28"
        }

    ]
}